Manny Seals did a Jubilee video.
>> 20 black conservatives versus her.
>> Yeah,
>> I don't know if Manny Seals is really
the right person to do a 20V black
conservative. She already got some weird
[ __ ] going on with Issa Ray and whole
bunch of other [ __ ] But I mean, you
picked who you picked. She know her [ __ ]
though. I tell I say that straight up.
Oh yeah. No, she know her [ __ ] cuz I'm
I'm like cuz I know she really do the
debate [ __ ] so I understand why they
picked her. I'm just like the optics is
like damn you couldn't find nobody [ __ ]
>> But it like every time I see [ __ ] like
that I just be like I used to get mad
like whenever I see Candace Owens Ben
Carson anybody black you know talking
about we don't need reparations or don't
worry about reparations and we we
reasons why we ain't you know we why we
ain't move forward and then like it's
always the three things. is either we
don't deserve reparations or we ain't
going to never get it.
>> Even like black culture is toxic.
There's a lot of that one. A lot of that
one.
>> And then it usually be like black man
[ __ ] ain't [ __ ] The regular [ __ ]
ain't [ __ ]
>> Fathers today they
>> all that all that [ __ ]
>> And I just feel like if you really
lived in a black community, this those
things would never even show up. got
cousins that's like grew up rich as
[ __ ]
>> Yeah.
>> But they were always whether they came
to see me, they came to Akan to stay
with my folks, stay with my daddy side
of the family, like they was always
around us. So they already saw how [ __ ]
was.
>> Yeah.
>> So it was they was never like even
though they was [ __ ] in Florida with
a gang of money, they was always around.
So they still saw
>> how [ __ ] Yeah. how [ __ ] really boy just
[ __ ] how [ __ ] really is cuz it's easy to
be like oh it just ain't nothing but
killers and drug dealers in the hood and
I'm like bro 80% of people is just
regular [ __ ] with jobs
>> regular